tripres.com 2001-12-25

# TripReservations.com - Your source for the best hotel room rate discounts in Las Vegas!

|   
---  
  
**TripReservations.com's E-Mail List**   
You will be notified of specials available from TripReservations.com!   
  
|  Your Privacy

At TripReservations.com, we are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect about you to process orders and to provide a more personalized travel experience. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy. 

**What information do we collect? How do we use it?**

  * When you reserve a hotel room we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card number, and expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your reservation request and to notify you of your reservation status. 
  * When you enter a contest or other promotional feature, we may ask for your name, address, and e-mail address so we can administer the contest and notify winners. 
  * We may also use the information we collect to occasionally notify you about important functionality changes to the Web site, new TripReservations.com services, and special offers we think you'll find valuable. 

**Does TripReservations.com protect customer information?**   
When you place orders or access your account information, we offer the use of secure encryption algorithms to protect sensitive data. The encryption algorithms encrypt all information you input before it is sent to us. Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access. 

**What about "cookies"?**   
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information, but they do enable us to provide special website features. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that. Even without a cookie, you can still use most of the features in our site. 

**Will TripReservations.com disclose the information it collects to outside parties?**   
TripReservations.com does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. We may choose to do so in the future with trustworthy third parties. Also, TripReservations.com may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information. 

**In summary**   
We are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect on the site to make travel with TripReservations.com possible and to enhance your overall travel experience. We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. We may choose to do so in the future with trustworthy third parties. 

**Your consent**   
By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by TripReservations.com. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

**Tell us what you think**   
TripReservations.com welcomes your questions and comments about privacy. Please send e-mail to [feedback@tripreservations.com](mailto:feedback@tripreservations.com&Subject=Website%20Feedback).   
  
Privacy Policy   |   Terms & Conditions   |   Employment          North America: **800-255-0372**     International: **+1-702-946-5200**   
All Rights Reserved. Copyright ©1998-2001 by TripReservations.com
